ibatrademart.com 2017-06-06

# Indian Brokers Association

Indian Brokers Association

IBA covers the Agro commodities, Non agro commodities, Animal & Poultry feed, Metal, Energy, Chemical, FMCG etc. in our industry structure.

### Exhibitions & Conferences

### Advertise Here

[Home](http://www.ibatrademart.com/) >> Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

IBA Trade Mart committed to you to maintain your privacy and security is our prior responsibility. We are making a numerous of efforts in order to improve our security and privacy policies as well and adopt various measures and techniques to provide you a secure and protective journey on our website. Please read the following Privacy policy in order to better understand how we are using your data and personal stuff as well. If you are using or access to this website than you are bound to follow these policies and if you do not want to agree these privacy policy than you are advised not to use this site. 

Changes

We may update our Privacy policy time to time without providing any prior notice. So, user(s) are solely responsible to maintain eye on the website periodically.

Data collection

IBA Trade Mart collects information of its users in order to provide the services and to intimate its users about online and offline offers as well. At the time of registration we may ask various personal identifying questions from the users such as name, email address, contact information, business information or any other business information. Once the user get registered on the website he/she shall no longer remain stranger to IBA Trade Mart and also it is deemed that the user gives the grant to IBA Trade Mart to publish or use their personal information throughout IBA Trade Mart’s marketplace including but not limited to directories, catalogs, trade leads etc. IBA Trade Mart includes various other links/networks on website for promotional purposes and whatsoever it will be, these other networks may sponsored by companies other than IBA Trade Mart or may be co-sponsored by IBA Trade Mart whatever will be the case may be we will may share your personal information with such promotional networks. It remains optional for you whether you want to participate in the promotions or not. 

How we make use of your personal information

The objective behind collecting your personal information is to provide our best services to our user(s) on our website. In order to provide you our best offers whether such offers are online or offline. Once we get know about user(s) personal information after the registration process we will start mailing, calling or messaging our user(S) business enquiry from various buyers and sellers whether they make you for you not. IBA Trade Mart does not have any control over the users who are sending business enquiries to our listed members. Also, we may use only that information which comes under the scope of our privacy policy and also under the applicable law. 

Disclosure Of information 

IBA Trade Mart only discloses your personal information in special circumstances along with a bonafide belief. As it was committed by IBA Trade Mart to maintains its responsibility for non-disclosure of information of the user(s) on the website for their security purpose, with respect to this provision IBA Trade Mart shall not display your email address on the market place in order to avoid any cyber mishap. Also, IBA Trade Mart may disclose your information for any legal proceeding or in case of any violation of terms and conditions or any policy has been made or if there is violation intellectual property rights of any other person or third party. It should be understood that personal information of the user’s may also be shared for the purpose of sale. We also may share your person information with third party in case if IBA Trade Mart getting emerged with any other business entity or there is any amalgamation, transmission, re-construction of business etc. You may not held IBA Trade Mart liable for any damages occurred damage occurred due to access on the third party website, you will held sole responsible for consequences occurred due to your access to another site. 

Account Management

User(s) of IBA Trade Mart shall manage their accounts as they have right to make corrections and amendments in their account provided by IBA Trade Mart by sending their matter concerned at info@ibamail.org IBA Trade Mart within 3days of receiving such request makes changes in the users account. The time period of 3days is allotted due to the online verification procedure and server cache policies. 

Security

IBA Trade Mart may employ various technical and physical measures in order to provide smooth and healthy security precautions to our user(s). IBA Trade Mart will not sell your personal information or sensitive data to any other third party through which one can misuse your provided information for the purpose of telemarketing, bulk mailing or any other wrong purpose which may give birth to any cyber offence. IBA Trade Mart will only sell your personal information if user’s consent has been received by us. The demographics that we may provide to our partners and advertisers regarding products and services shall not include any personal identified information. We are requested you not to disclose the password of your account managed under this site and to properly close the browser window so that no one can access your personal information via any correspondence. 

Agreement

After accessing to this website you are bound with the terms and conditions and privacy policies provided by IBA Trade Mart.
